Guide to the Emilie F. Miller papers, 1987-1991
George Mason University Libraries
- Emilie F.Miller Collection
  - Richmond [Report] 1991 (Folder 10, Box 6)
  - Richmond City Help Traffic (Folder 11, Box 6)
  - Richmond Letter July 25,1991 (Folder 12, Box 6)
  - Richmond Visit's 1990 (Folder 13, Box 6)
  - Virginia's Right to Work (Folder 14, Box 6)
  - Road Allocation, Fairfax County (Folder 15, Box 6)
  - Robb Charles ,Senate Race and Government of Virginia (Folder 16, Box 6)
  - Robb Charles Lectures (Folder 17, Box 6)
  - Robb Charles, Senate (Folder 18, Box 6)
  - Rotary Club (Folder 19, Box 6)
  - Route 123 Improvement Project (Folder 20, Box 6)
  - Route 28 [Ground Breaking and Project] (Folder 21, Box 6)
  - Route 58 [ Contract and Studies] (Folder 22, Box 6)
  - Sales Tax (Folder 23, Box 6)
  - School Based Clinics (Folder 24, Box 6)
  - School Bus Uses (Folder 25, Box 6)
  - Science [ Educational Policies for National Survival] (Folder 26, Box 6)
  - Scouts [Boy Scouts Organization] (Folder 27, Box 6)
  - Scott Silverthorne [Correspondence] February 20, 1990 (Folder 28, Box 6)
  - Senate Democratic Caucus 1991 (Folder 29, Box 6)
  - Senator Dick Saslaw (Folder 30, Box 6)
  - Senate Page [Resolution and Applications] 1989 (Folder 31, Box 6)
  - Senate Page Selection 1990 (Folder 32, Box 6)
  - Senate Pages 1991 (Folder 33, Box 6)
  - Senate Tracking Forms (Folder 34, Box 6)
  - Senior Citizens [ Resource Management for Seniors] (Folder 35, Box 6)
  - Sensible Washington Area Transportation Coalition (Folder 36, Box 6)
  - Sexual Assault Report (Folder 37, Box 6)
  - International Council of Shopping Centers (Folder 38, Box 6)
  - Sidewalks Repair (Folder 39, Box 6)
  - Singleton for Sheriff Campaign (Folder 40, Box 6)
  - Small Claims Court (Folder 41, Box 6)
  - Smart Card International (Folder 42, Box 6)
  - Snow Removal [Virginia Department of Transportation] (Folder 43, Box 6)
  - Social Center (Folder 44, Box 6)
  - Social Security Historical Data (Folder 45, Box 6)
  - Social Services (Folder 46, Box 6)
  - Southern Growth Policies Board (Folder 47, Box 6)
  - Southern Legislative Conference [1 of 4] (Folder 48, Box 6)
  - Southern Legislative Conference [2 of 4] (Folder 49, Box 6)
  - Southern Legislative Conference [3 of 4] (Folder 50, Box 6)
  - Southern Legislative Conference [4 of 4] (Folder 51, Box 6)
  - Southern Legislative Conference Committee on Human Resources 1990 (Folder 52, Box 6)
  - Southern Legislative Conference August 25,1988 (Folder 53, Box 6)
  - Southern Legislative Summit :Healthy Infants and Families (Folder 54, Box 6)
  - Southern Regional Education Board (Folder 55, Box 6)
  - Virginia Space Activities (Folder 56, Box 6)
  - Speeches and Testimony [1 of 2] (Folder 57, Box 6)
  - Speeches and Testimony [2 of 2] (Folder 58, Box 6)
  - Speeches and Testimony: Central Fairfax Chamber (Folder 59, Box 6)
  - Speeches and Testimony: Commission on Educational Opportunity for all Virginians (Folder 60, Box 6)
  - Speeches and Testimony Disabled Virginians (Folder 61, Box 6)
  - Speeches and Testimony:Mental Health,Mental Retardation and Substance Abuse Services [1 of 2] (Folder 62, Box 6)
  - Speeches and Testimony:Mental Health,Mental Retardation and Substance Abuse Services [2 of 2] (Folder 63, Box 6)
  - Speeches and Testimony:Taxes (Folder 64, Box 6)
  - Speeches and Testimony:Budget and Forecasting (Folder 65, Box 6)
  - Speeches and Testimony:Volunteers (Folder 66, Box 6)
  - Speeches: Highlights of the Comprehensive State Plan for Mental Health,Mental Retardation (Folder 67, Box 6)
  - Senate Resolution for Board Nominations (Folder 68, Box 6)
  - Spotlight on Arts (Folder 1, Box 7)
  - Springfield Bypass [News Clip] (Folder 2, Box 7)
  - St.Ambrose Church (Folder 3, Box 7)
  - State Mental Health,Mental Retardation Board Resignation Letter Emilie F.Miller January 11,1987 (Folder 4, Box 7)
  - State Bug...House Bill 1519 (Folder 5, Box 7)
  - Standards of Care House Bill 1077 [Carried Over] (Folder 6, Box 7)
  - State Flower - Dogwood (Folder 7, Box 7)
  - Stop Child Abuse Now - SCAN (Folder 8, Box 7)
  - Straight, Inc. [Drug Treatment Program] (Folder 9, Box 7)
  - Surrogate Motherhood (Folder 10, Box 7)
  - Sydni Am Shollenberger, Public Relations [Resume] (Folder 11, Box 7)
  - Fairfax City - Oil Tank Farm Correspondence (Folder 12, Box 7)
  - Fairfax City - Oil Tank Farm Leak [1 of 3] (Folder 13, Box 7)
  - Fairfax City - Oil Tank Farm Leak [2 of 3] (Folder 14, Box 7)
  - Fairfax City - Oil Tank Farm Leak [3 of 3] (Folder 15, Box 7)
  - Taxes [State and Local Taxes] [1 of 2] (Folder 16, Box 7)
  - Taxes [State and Local Taxes] [2 of 2] (Folder 17, Box 7)
  - " Is Virginia a High -Tax State ?", State Taxes (Folder 18, Box 7)
  - Taxpayers Association [Virginia] (Folder 19, Box 7)
  - Teen Health Center (Folder 20, Box 7)
  - Teen Pregnancy (Folder 21, Box 7)
  - Teen Suicide (Folder 22, Box 7)
  - Term Limitation (Folder 23, Box 7)
  - Terry,Mary Sue [Attorney General ,Virginia] (Folder 24, Box 7)
  - Thomas Jefferson High School for Science and Technology (Folder 25, Box 7)
  - Timberlane Elementary School (Folder 26, Box 7)
  - Tobacco Company (Folder 27, Box 7)
  - Toll Road Corporation of Virginia (Folder 28, Box 7)
  - Tort Reform [Correspondence] (Folder 29, Box 7)
  - Tourism Industry (Folder 30, Box 7)
  - Town Meeting ,[Attended People] (Folder 31, Box 7)
  - Transfer Tax [1 of 2] (Folder 32, Box 7)
  - Transfer Tax [2 of 2] (Folder 33, Box 7)
  - Transportation [Companies ,Issues,Projects in Virginia][1 of 2] (Folder 34, Box 7)
  - Transportation [Companies ,Issues,Projects in Virginia][2 of 2] (Folder 35, Box 7)
  - Transportation Pledge Bonds (Folder 36, Box 7)
  - Trucks [Reports of Truck's Traffic] (Folder 37, Box 7)
  - TRW Federal Systems Group [Brochure] (Folder 38, Box 7)
  - Tuition Assistance [Newspaper Clip] (Folder 39, Box 7)
  - Twenty First Century - Study [State Council of Higher Education] (Folder 40, Box 7)
  - Tytran - Tyson's Transportation Association (Folder 41, Box 7)
  - United Airlines [Facility Location] (Folder 42, Box 7)
  - Union of Concerned Scientists [Voter Information Kit] (Folder 43, Box 7)
  - Vanguard Services Unlimited [Demeter House] (Folder 44, Box 7)
  - Vegetation Control Act (Folder 45, Box 7)
  - Veterans [Department of Veteran Affairs] (Folder 46, Box 7)
  - Victim Assistance [Virginia Network] (Folder 47, Box 7)
  - Virginia Alcohol Safety Action Program (Folder 48, Box 7)
  - Virginia AFL-CIO [American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations] (Folder 49, Box 7)
  - Virginia Association for the Deaf (Folder 50, Box 7)
  - Virginia Association of Community Services Boards [VACSB] (Folder 51, Box 7)
  - Virginia Association of Consumer Affairs Administrators (Folder 52, Box 7)
  - Virginia Association of Female Executives [VAFE] (Folder 53, Box 7)
  - Virginia Association of Marriage and Family Therapist (Folder 54, Box 7)
  - Virginia Association of Realtors Legislative (Folder 55, Box 7)
  - Virginia Citizens Consumer Council (Folder 56, Box 7)
  - Virginia Citizens for a Sound Economy (Folder 57, Box 7)
  - Virginia Commission for the Arts (Folder 58, Box 7)
  - Virginia Community Colleges (Folder 59, Box 7)
  - Virginia Council on Human Rights (Folder 60, Box 7)
  - Virginia Cultural Laureate (Folder 61, Box 7)
  - Woodrow Wilson Rehabilitation Center [WWRC] (Folder 62, Box 7)
  - Woodson High School (Folder 63, Box 7)
  - Working for Sex Equity in Insurance Information and Strategy Packet (Folder 64, Box 7)
  - Workman's Compensation (Folder 65, Box 7)
  - Young Democrats (Folder 66, Box 7)
  - Youth for Tomorrow [Joe Gibbs] (Folder 67, Box 7)
  - Youth Service Commission (Folder 68, Box 7)
  - Zip Codes (Folder 69, Box 7)
  - Virginia Department of Youth Services (Folder 1, Box 8)
  - Virginia Education Association 1991 (Folder 2, Box 8)
  - Virginia Education Financing (Folder 3, Box 8)
  - Virginia Federation of Parents for Drug Free Youth (Folder 4, Box 8)
  - Virginia Firearms Dealers Association (Folder 5, Box 8)
  - Virginia Forestry and Forest Products Council Legislative (Folder 6, Box 8)
  - Virginia Gasoline and Automobile Repair Association (Folder 7, Box 8)
  - Virginia Governmental Employers Association (Folder 8, Box 8)
  - Virginia Historical Society (Folder 9, Box 8)
  - Virginia Home Care Alliance (Folder 10, Box 8)
  - Virginia Hospital Association (Folder 11, Box 8)
  - Virginia Inland Ports (Folder 12, Box 8)
  - Virginia Liaison Office (Folder 13, Box 8)
  - Virginia Museum of Natural History (Folder 14, Box 8)
  - Virginia Prenatal Association (Folder 15, Box 8)
  - Virginia Petroleum Council - Requirements for Driver (Folder 16, Box 8)
  - Virginia Power [Dominion Resources] (Folder 17, Box 8)
  - Virginia Retail Merchants Association [Others] (Folder 18, Box 8)
  - Virginia Retirement System (Folder 19, Box 8)
  - Virginia Review [Journal] (Folder 20, Box 8)
  - Virginia School Board Associations (Folder 21, Box 8)
  - Virginia School Bus Association [Others] (Folder 22, Box 8)
  - Virginia Service Station Dealers (Folder 23, Box 8)
  - Virginia Silver Star Foundation (Folder 24, Box 8)
  - Virginia Small Business Financing Authority (Folder 25, Box 8)
  - Virginia State Police Association (Folder 26, Box 8)
  - Virginia Supplemental Retirement System - Annual Report June, 1988 (Folder 27, Box 8)
  - Virginia TaxPayers Association (Folder 28, Box 8)
  - Virginia Treatment Center for Children (Folder 29, Box 8)
  - Virginia Water Projects Inc (Folder 30, Box 8)
  - Virginia Women Attorney's Association - VWAA (Folder 31, Box 8)
  - Virginia Women's Network (Folder 32, Box 8)
  - Virginia Organization to Keep Abortion Legal - VOKAL (Folder 33, Box 8)
  - Volunteers- [Department of Volunteerism and Others] (Folder 34, Box 8)
  - Voter Fraud [Electoral Board] (Folder 35, Box 8)
  - Voter Registration (Folder 36, Box 8)
  - Washington Gas Light Company - Annual Report (Folder 37, Box 8)
  - Waste Management [1 of 2] (Folder 38, Box 8)
  - Waste Management [2 of 2] (Folder 39, Box 8)
  - Waste Management and Recycling Correspondence (Folder 40, Box 8)
  - Waste Management - Water Issues (Folder 41, Box 8)
  - Virginia Water Resources Center Research (Folder 42, Box 8)
  - Welfare and Social Services (Folder 43, Box 8)
  - Governor Wilder [1 of 2] (Folder 44, Box 8)
  - Governor Wilder [2 of 2] (Folder 45, Box 8)
  - Women Legislators Lobby - WiLL (Folder 46, Box 8)
  - William and Mary College [Alumni Chapter] (Folder 47, Box 8)
  - William Earl.C [BDM Company President] (Folder 48, Box 8)
  - Williamsburg Commemorative Session (Folder 49, Box 8)
  - S.B.657 - Wine Franchise Act (Folder 50, Box 8)
  - Were Northern Virginia Television - WNVT (Folder 51, Box 8)
  - Frank Wolf, Congressman (Folder 52, Box 8)
  - Women in General Assembly (Folder 53, Box 8)
  - Virginia Council on Status of Women (Folder 54, Box 8)
  - Women's Campaign Fund (Folder 55, Box 8)
  - Women's Center (Folder 56, Box 8)
  - Women's Equity Action League - WEAL (Folder 57, Box 8)
  - Women's Issues (Folder 58, Box 8)
  - WETA - WNVC 56 Developing Images (Folder 59, Box 8)
  - Women's Issues [1 of 4] (Folder 60, Box 8)
  - Women's Issues [2 of 4] (Folder 61, Box 8)
  - Women's Issues [3 of 4] (Folder 62, Box 8)
  - Women's Issues [4 of 4] (Folder 63, Box 8)
  - Women's Issues in 1991 1991 (Folder 64, Box 8)
  - Women's Rountable [1 of 3] 1991 (Folder 65, Box 8)
  - Women's Rountable [2 of 3] 1990 (Folder 66, Box 8)
  - Women's Rountable [3 of 3] 1989 (Folder 67, Box 8)
  - Women's Issues - Organizations (Folder 68, Box 8)
  - Women's Lobbying Group (Folder 69, Box 8)
  - Woodrow Wilson Bridge Improvement 1990 (Folder 70, Box 8)
  - Woodrow Wilson College Establishment (Folder 71, Box 8)
  - Arctic National Wildlife Refuge - ANWR (Folder 1, Box 9)
  - Business - Higher Education Forum (Folder 2, Box 9)
  - Center for Policy Alternatives (Folder 3, Box 9)
  - Center for American Women in Politics- CAWP [1 of 2] (Folder 4, Box 9)
  - Center for American Women in Politics- CAWP [2 of 2] (Folder 5, Box 9)
  - CAWP Forum for Women State Legislators November 14, 1991 (Folder 6, Box 9)
  - Stationary of Emilie F.Miller (Folder 7, Box 9)
  - Democratic Committee Platform Hearing [1 of 4] 1991 (Folder 8, Box 9)
  - Democratic Committee Platform Hearing [2 of 4] 1992 (Folder 9, Box 9)
  - Democratic Committee Platform Hearing [3 of 4] 1992 (Folder 10, Box 9)
  - Democratic Committee Platform Hearing [4 of 4] 1992 (Folder 11, Box 9)
  - Developing the Agenda ,Framing the Message: A Roundtable for Pro-Choice State Legislators (Folder 12, Box 9)
  - Global Leaders for the South ,1989 1989 (Folder 13, Box 9)
  - Global Leaders for the South: A BellSouth Leadership Forum [1 of 2] (Folder 14, Box 9)
  - Global Leaders for the South: A BellSouth Leadership Forum [2 of 2] (Folder 15, Box 9)
  - Global Leaders of the South, Washington.D.C. November 10, 1991 (Folder 16, Box 9)
  - Global Leaders for the South 1991 (Folder 17, Box 9)
  - Global Leaders for the South 1992 (Folder 18, Box 9)
  - Global Leaders for the South [1 of 2] 1993 (Folder 19, Box 9)
  - Global Leaders for the South [2 of 2] 1993 (Folder 20, Box 9)
  - Global Leaders for the South 1994 (Folder 21, Box 9)
  - Global Leaders for the South: Alumni Directory (Folder 22, Box 9)
  - Governor's Council on Adolescent Pregnancy (Folder 23, Box 9)
  - Advocating and Building Coalitions [ABC] - Conference (Folder 24, Box 9)
  - Mental Health and Mental Retardation Conference List 1985 (Folder 25, Box 9)
  - Emilie F.Miller Office Copies (Folder 26, Box 9)
  - Human Services Committee NCSL State Federal Assembly [1 of 2] May 17,1990 (Folder 1, Box 10)
  - Human Services Committee NCSL State Federal Assembly [2 of 2] May 17,1990 (Folder 2, Box 10)
  - Medical Research [Articles] (Folder 3, Box 10)
  - National Conference of State Legislatures(NCSL) - Labor Issues [1 of 2] December 2,1989 (Folder 4, Box 10)
  - National Conference of State Legislatures(NCSL) - Labor Issues [2 of 2] December 2,1989 (Folder 5, Box 10)
  - Quest for Success [ National Alumni Junior Achievement Association] (Folder 6, Box 10)
  - Report of the Commission on the Skills of the American Workforce June 12 ,1991 (Folder 7, Box 10)
  - SouthEast US - Korea Joint Economic Conference 1990 (Folder 8, Box 10)
  - Southern Growth [Global Leaders for South] (Folder 9, Box 10)
  - Southern Legislative Conference - Human Resources Committee Business Meeting (Folder 10, Box 10)
  - Southern Legislative Conference - Human Resources Committee July, 1989 (Folder 11, Box 10)
  - State of States Symposium ,Charlottesville [1 of 2] December 7,1990 (Folder 12, Box 10)
  - State of States Symposium ,Charlottesville [2 of 2] December 7,1990 (Folder 13, Box 10)
  - Taking Charge of America's Future [Draft] (Folder 14, Box 10)
  - The Impact of Women in Public Office [Report] (Folder 15, Box 10)
  - Women's Campaign Fund - Strategic Leadership, Harvard University December 10,1989 (Folder 16, Box 10)
  - Women's Campaign Fund - Strategic Leadership ,Conference 1990 (Folder 17, Box 10)
  - Women's Campaign Research Fund - WCRF (Folder 18, Box 10)
  - 18th Statewide Conference Department of Mental Health and Mental Retardation (Folder 19, Box 10)
  - St.Petersburg Trip Report June 3, 1995 (Folder 20, Box 10)
  - Report of the Dialogues and Programs of the INET Foundation in Russia 1993 - 1994 (Folder 21, Box 10)
  - 1990 Virginia Inauguration 1990 (Folder 22, Box 10)
  - Women's Research Institute [Annual Reports] (Folder 23, Box 10)
  - Women's Research Institute [Virginia Polytechnic Institute] (Folder 24, Box 10)
  - Maryland Project for Women and Politics [1 of 3] (Folder 25, Box 10)
  - Maryland Project for Women and Politics [2 of 3] (Folder 26, Box 10)
  - Maryland Project for Women and Politics [3 of 3] (Folder 27, Box 10)
  - Budget Amendments April 3, 1991 (Folder 1, Box 11)
  - Budget Bill and Spreadsheets [1 of 6] 1991 (Folder 2, Box 11)
  - Budget Bill and Spreadsheets [2 of 6] 1991 (Folder 3, Box 11)
  - Budget Bill and Spreadsheets [3 of 6] 1991 (Folder 4, Box 11)
  - Budget Bill and Spreadsheets [4 of 6] 1991 (Folder 5, Box 11)
  - Budget Bill and Spreadsheets [5 of 6] 1991 (Folder 6, Box 11)
  - Budget Bill and Spreadsheets [6 of 6] 1991 (Folder 7, Box 11)
  - Chief Patron Reports [1 of 4] 1988 - 1991 (Folder 8, Box 11)
  - Chief Patron Reports [2 of 4] 1988 - 1991 (Folder 9, Box 11)
  - Chief Patron Reports [3 of 4] 1988 - 1991 (Folder 10, Box 11)
  - Chief Patron Reports [4 of 4] 1988 - 1991 (Folder 11, Box 11)
  - Joint Conference Committee Reports on House Bills 1991 (Folder 12, Box 11)
  - Joint Conference Committee Reports on Senate Bills 1991 (Folder 13, Box 11)
  - Education and Health Committee ,Elementary School Guidance Counselors 1989 (Folder 14, Box 11)
  - Education and Health - Higher Education Sub Committee [1 of 2] 1988 (Folder 15, Box 11)
  - Education and Health - Higher Education Sub Committee [2 of 2] 1988 (Folder 16, Box 11)
  - Education and Health Committee - Senate Joint Resolution 63 1989 (Folder 17, Box 11)
  - Education and Health Committee - Senate Joint Resolution 99 1989 (Folder 18, Box 11)
  - Fairfax City Requested Budget Amendment (Folder 19, Box 11)
  - Fairfax County Board - Legislative Tracking 1991 (Folder 20, Box 11)
  - Fairfax County Public Schools Legislative Report 1991 (Folder 21, Box 11)
  - Future Legislative Proposals (Folder 22, Box 11)
  - General Assembly in 1989 1989 (Folder 23, Box 11)
  - General Assembly in 1990 1990 (Folder 24, Box 11)
  - General Assembly Legislative Services and Policy 1990 (Folder 25, Box 11)
  - General Laws Committee [1 of 2] 1988 (Folder 26, Box 11)
  - General Laws Committee [2 of 2] 1988 (Folder 27, Box 11)
  - Higher Education Council Legislative Tracking (Folder 28, Box 11)
  - Local Government Committee [1 of 2] 1988 (Folder 29, Box 11)
  - Local Government Committee [2 of 2] 1988 (Folder 30, Box 11)
  - Miller Record [1987] 1987 (Folder 31, Box 11)
  - Miller Record [Pre-1987] (Folder 32, Box 11)
  - Miller Record Correspondence [1 of 2] 1988 (Folder 33, Box 11)
  - Miller Record Correspondence [2 of 2] 1988 (Folder 34, Box 11)
  - Miller Record Correspondence [1 of 2] 1989 (Folder 1, Box 12)
  - Miller Record Correspondence [2 of 2] 1989 (Folder 2, Box 12)
  - Miller Record Printed Materials [1 of 2] 1988 (Folder 3, Box 12)
  - Miller Record Printed Materials [2 of 2] 1988 (Folder 4, Box 12)
  - Miller Record Printed Materials [1 of 5] 1989 (Folder 5, Box 12)
  - Miller Record Printed Materials [2 of 5] 1989 (Folder 6, Box 12)
  - Miller Record Printed Materials [3 of 5] 1989 (Folder 7, Box 12)
  - Miller Record Printed Materials [4 of 5] 1989 (Folder 8, Box 12)
  - Miller Record Printed Materials [5 of 5] 1989 (Folder 9, Box 12)
  - Oath of Office January 13, 1988 (Folder 10, Box 12)
  - Proposed Legislation :Health Planning, Sen. Emilie Miller - GAB Rm381. January 23, 1989 (Folder 11, Box 12)
  - Miller Record Correspondence [ 1 of 3] 1990 (Folder 12, Box 12)
  - Miller Record Correspondence [2 of 3] 1990 (Folder 13, Box 12)
  - Miller Record Correspondence [3 of 3] 1990 (Folder 14, Box 12)
  - Miller Record [1 of 2] 1991 (Folder 15, Box 12)
  - Miller Records [2 0f 2] 1991 (Folder 16, Box 12)
  - Miller Records [1992] 1992 (Folder 17, Box 12)
  - Resolutions (Folder 18, Box 12)
  - Restroom - Lounge for Women Senators 1990 (Folder 19, Box 12)
  - Senate Bill # 173 - Federal Retirees Tax Exemption 1988 (Folder 20, Box 12)
  - Senate Guidelines for Conference Attendance (Folder 21, Box 12)
  - Senate Matters (Folder 22, Box 12)
  - Senate Miscellaneous (Folder 23, Box 12)
  - Southern Governors Conference Infant Mortality [1 of 4] 1990 (Folder 24, Box 12)
  - Southern Governors Conference Infant Mortality [2 of 4] 1990 (Folder 25, Box 12)
  - Southern Governors Conference Infant Mortality [3 of 4] 1990 (Folder 26, Box 12)
  - Southern Governors Conference Infant Mortality [4 of 4] 1990 (Folder 27, Box 12)
  - Votes [How They Voted on Women's Issue in 1988] 1988 (Folder 28, Box 12)
  - Votes [in 1991] 1991 (Folder 29, Box 12)
  - Miller Record [1990's] (Folder 30, Box 12)
  - Acupuncture Correspondence 1991 (Folder 1, Box 13)
  - Arts Funding [1 of 7] 1991 (Folder 2, Box 13)
  - Arts Funding [2 of 7] 1991 (Folder 3, Box 13)
  - Arts Funding [3 of 7] 1991 (Folder 4, Box 13)
  - Arts Funding [4 of 7] 1991 (Folder 5, Box 13)
  - Arts Funding [5 of 7] 1991 (Folder 6, Box 13)
  - Arts Funding [6 of 7] 1991 (Folder 7, Box 13)
  - Arts Funding [7 of 7] 1991 (Folder 8, Box 13)
  - Replies to Budget Cuts and Funding 1991 (Folder 9, Box 13)
  - Co-Patron of S.B.503 ,[Gartlan], Statute of Limitation- Sexual Child Abuse (Folder 10, Box 13)
  - NOVA Public Hearing Correspondence 1991 (Folder 11, Box 13)
  - Correspondence To Proposed Cuts in Arts Funding January 17,1991 (Folder 12, Box 13)
  - Correspondence To Proposed Cuts in Arts Funding January 18,1991 (Folder 13, Box 13)
  - Correspondence [1 of 5] January 29,1991 (Folder 14, Box 13)
  - Correspondence [2 of 5] January 31,1991 (Folder 15, Box 13)
  - Correspondence [3 of 5] February 12,1991 (Folder 16, Box 13)
  - Correspondence [4 of 5] February 19,1991 (Folder 17, Box 13)
  - Correspondence [5 of 5] February 21,1991 (Folder 18, Box 13)
  - Dental Hygienists (Folder 19, Box 13)
  - Elected School Boards Grievance Procedure (Folder 20, Box 13)
  - Fair Elections Practices Correspondence (Folder 21, Box 13)
  - General Correspondence [1 of 2] January ,1991 (Folder 22, Box 13)
  - General Correspondence [2 of 2] February,1991 (Folder 23, Box 13)
  - Gun Legislation 1991 1991 (Folder 24, Box 13)
  - House Bill 541 - Funding for Circuit Court Support Services 1991 (Folder 25, Box 13)
  - Replies :House Bill 1308 - Asset Forfeiture Sharing 1991 (Folder 26, Box 13)
  - House Bill: 335 Insurance Correspondence [1 of 3] 1991 (Folder 27, Box 13)
  - House Bill: 335 Insurance Correspondence [2 of 3] 1991 (Folder 28, Box 13)
  - House Bill: 335 Insurance Correspondence [3 of 3] 1991 (Folder 29, Box 13)
  - House Bill 1273- Local Zoning Restrictions on Rehab Centers (Folder 30, Box 13)
  - House Bill 315 - Malpractice Cap Correspondence (Folder 31, Box 13)
  - Mechanics Lien Laws Correspondence [1 of 2] 1991 (Folder 32, Box 13)
  - Mechanics Lien Laws Correspondence [2 of 2] 1991 (Folder 33, Box 13)
  - Mental Health,Mental Retardation ,Substance Abuse Services Correspondence 1991 (Folder 34, Box 13)
  - Off Track Betting Correspondence 1991 (Folder 35, Box 13)
  - State Bill 235 - Open Supply and Divorcement Correspondence 1991 (Folder 36, Box 13)
  - Parental Notification Correspondence 1991 (Folder 37, Box 13)
  - Physical Therapy - Direct Access 1991 (Folder 38, Box 13)
  - State Bill 660 - Recycling [Gartlan] [1 of 2] 1991 (Folder 39, Box 13)
  - State Bill 660 - Recycling [Gartlan] [2 of 2] 1991 (Folder 40, Box 13)
  - State Bill 444 [Share the Ride] 1990 (Folder 41, Box 13)
  - School Counselors 1991 (Folder 42, Box 13)
  - Senator Bill 502- Bottle Bill (Folder 43, Box 13)
  - Share The Ride Correspondence 1991 (Folder 44, Box 13)
  - Re: Transfer of Monies from Highway Trust to General Fund 1991 (Folder 45, Box 13)
  - United Airlines Maintenance Facility 1991 (Folder 46, Box 13)
  - General Correspondence [1 of 2] (Folder 47, Box 13)
  - General Correspondence [2 of 2] (Folder 48, Box 13)
  - Affordable Housing Letters 1990 (Folder 1, Box 14)
  - Anita B.Glover ,Virginia Department of Taxation Correspondence 1991 (Folder 2, Box 14)
  - Boards and Commission Recommendations [1 of 4] (Folder 3, Box 14)
  - Boards and Commission Recommendations [2 of 4] (Folder 4, Box 14)
  - Boards and Commission Recommendations [3 of 4] (Folder 5, Box 14)
  - Boards and Commission Recommendations [4 of 4] (Folder 6, Box 14)
  - Brian Dion - Gift Lot Subdivision (Folder 7, Box 14)